centova.com 2011-05-27

# Centova Technologies Inc. - Privacy Policy

Centova Technologies Inc. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for centova.com and centova.net.

**Use of Personal Information**

Any personal information provided by visitors to Centova Technologies Inc. will be provided on a completely voluntary basis. No information about visitors to this site or customers of Centova Technologies Inc. shall be sold or released to any third parties without prior consent, except as required by law.

Information provided to Centova Technologies Inc. by its clients will be used solely for the purposes of account administration and billing. When necessary, contact information is used to get in touch with the client from time to time. All correspondence will be related to the client's account; no unsolicted bulk E-mail will be sent.

**Mailing Lists, Discusson Groups, Subscriptions**

You will not under any circumstances be added to any mailing lists without your express consent. If you do decide to subscribe to any of our mailing lists or discussion groups, you may opt-out, or unsubscribe at any time using the simple procedure outlined when you subscribe.

**Use of Cookies**

We do make use of Internet Cookies for the sole purpose purpose of granting access to the member areas of our web-based services. These cookies do not persist across sessions, and are used solely for authentication purposes.  

**Logging of Personal Information**

Like all Internet servers, our web server records the date, time, and IP address of all connections made to our site. Except in cases of abuse to our system, we do not make any attempt to associate these IP addresses with individual users. These logs are used to generate aggregate reports of website usage. These reports do not contain any personally identifiable information. 

**Third Parties**

We do not make use of any third-party advertising schemes on our main website. We do not allow downloads and/or cookies from any third-party websites or advertisers on our site.

This site may contain links to other sites which are not under our control. Centova Technologies Inc. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites.

**Inquiries**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:

**Steve Blinch  
Centova Technologies Inc.
